Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and other media, 1880 -- 2000; 1915 -- 1999; MS024.007; 34.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 58 Audiovisual Object(s); 727 Digital Object(s)
  - MacJannet photographs, 1925 -- 1942; MS024.007.095
    - A young driver behind the wheel of the MacJannet School bus, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03676; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - An interior view of classrooms at the Elms School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03677; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      Buildings; Schools; Rooms; People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet students and staff on camels in during a trip to North Africa, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03678; Wide World Photos (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Staff; Students; Camels; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Young students performing a dance at the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03679; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Students; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Students in costume at the MacJannet School, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03680; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      taken from MS024/007-095#013 - "MacJannet School;" Jean and Emory Foster are located in the far right corner of the photograph
      People; Students; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; Foster, Emory; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Two young dancers at the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03681; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
    - Jean and Emory Foster touring ancient ruins with MacJannet students and staff, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03682; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Staff; Students; Ruins; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; Foster, Emory; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet School students, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03683; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Young dancers at the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03684; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    - MacJannet School children applauding Amelia Earhart during her visit to St. Cloud, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03706; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
      taken from MS024/007-095#014 - "MacJannet School." Donald MacJannet and Emory and Jean Foster are seen in the background of the photo.
      People; Staff; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Earhart, Amelia; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet students playing instruments, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03707; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
      taken from MS024/007-095#015 - "MacJannet School"
      People; Students; Instruments; Music and musical performances; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Woody Woodworth surrounded by MacJannet students on a passenger ferry, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03709; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Students; Boats and boating; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Emory and Jean Foster visiting ancient ruins in northern Africa with MacJannet students, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03710; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Students; Ruins; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Racing down the Biskra Sand Dunes in northern Africa, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03711; Wide World Photos (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Staff; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Donald MacJannet and others riding camels in Biskra, Algeria, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03712; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Staff; Students; Camels; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - A game of basketball at the Elms School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03713; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      MS024/007-095#016 - "MacJannet School"
      People; Students; Athletics; Basketball; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Peggy and Anne Murray posing in their ballerina costumes at the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03714; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      taken from MS024:007-095#016 - "MacJannet School"
      People; Students; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Murray, Peggy; Murray, Anne; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet students during a visit to the walled city of Carcassonne, France, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03715; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
      taken from MS024/007-095#016 - "MacJannet School"
    - MacJannet School staff members and students standing in front of the entrance to the walled city of Carcassonne, France, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03716; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      taken from MS024/007-095#017 - "MacJannet School"
      People; Staff; Students; City gates; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Two MacJannet School students in the snow, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03717; New York times (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    - MacJannet students brushing their teeth, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03718; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
    - MacJannet School staff and students listening to a young violinist, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03719; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
      People; Staff; Students; Music and musical performances; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Two young students at the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03720; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
      taken from MS024/007-095#018 - "MacJannet School"
  - Photographs of the MacJannet camp, 1926 -- 1955; MS024.007.096
    Most of the photographs are from the 1930s.
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00001 (Box 96)
      Most of the photos are from the 1930s camp seasons in Tailloires. Many duplicates.
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00002 (Box 96)
      Most of the photos are from the 1930s camp seasons in Talloires. Many duplicates.
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00003 (Box 96)
      Most of the photos are from the 1930s camp season in Talloires. Many duplicates.
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00004 (Box 96)
      Most of the photos are from the 1930s. Many duplicates.
      Children; MacJannet Camp
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00005 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00006 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00007 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00009 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00010 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00011 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00012 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00013 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00014 (Box 96)
    - Photos of the MacJannet summer camp, 1935; MS024.007.096.00015 (Box 96)
    - Lake dwellers pageant at MacJannet Camp, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04087; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      From MS024/007-096.
      Children; People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Children of the MacJannet Camps visit the Chateau de St. Bernard, 1955; MS024.007.DO.04088; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      Children; People; Castles; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Pageant archers taker aim at the MacJannet Camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04089; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      Children; People; Archery; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Race at the MacJannet Camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04090; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      From MS024/007-096
      Children; People; Races; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet campers on a trip with the MacJannet bus, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04091; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      2 copies from MS024/007-096.
    - Chalet 4, Les Libellules, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04092; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      From MS024/007-096. Names from the back: Nadia Laurilier (?), Madeleine Fontaine, Christiane Leroy, Nicole Urmes (?), Suzette Menard, Calude Grandmaire.
    - MacJannet campers relax in a tent, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04093; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      Children; People; Tents; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Beginning of Upper Camp, 1926; MS024.007.DO.04094; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      People; Cabins; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet campers Daniel Bouteille, Jean Lespinas, Maurice Rouchy, Christian Menard, Francis Demigueux, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04095; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    - MacJannet campers Francis Oizth, Jacques Noirid, Christiane Bazzere, Jacques Beaumont, Dominique Lapierre, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04096; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    - Admiring the view towards La Tournette on a MacJannet camp hike, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04097; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      People; Children; Views; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet chalet 3, les Abeilles, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04098; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      From MS024/007-096. Label on back: Anne-Marie Delorme, Francine Deronsseaux, Colette Delasbus, Marie Etchevogusea, Francoise Bouniot, Jacqueline Nugues, Marlyse Schwab, Razninde Angst, Rolande Santerre.
      --Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
    - MacJannet chalet 5, les Ecureuils, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04099; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      From MS024/007-096. Label on back: Christiane Rotinger, Joceline Biet, Michel Chaput, Josette Sident, Francoise Vergues, France-Marie Haunaux, Guillemette Doat, Genevieve Andrieux.
    - Exercises at the MacJannet camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04100; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
      People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet personal color snapshots, 1955 -- 1999; MS024.007.097 (Box 97)
  - MacJannet personal color snapshots, 1955 -- 1999; MS024.007.098 (Box 98)
  - MacJannet photographs, 1910 -- 1991; MS024.007.099
    Photos from scrapbooks and mini albums. Includes MacJannet Foundation meeting photos. Includes family photographs of the Blensdorf family.
    - Tufts honorary ceremony at the Priory at Talloires, 1980; MS024.007.099.00001 (Box 99)
      People; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Tufts in Talloires
    - Mini album, Charlotte MacJannet in Paris, 1990; MS024.007.099.00002 (Box 99)
      Includes photos of Emory Foster's (D. MacJannet's brother-in-law) grave.
      People; Buildings; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Mini photograph album - wedding, 1989; MS024.007.099.00003 (Box 99)
      Album probaly sent to Charlotte MacJannet
      People
    - Photos of MacJannet Foundation meeting at Priory, 1985; MS024.007.099.00004 (Box 99)
      From mini album.
      MacJannet Foundation
    - Photos of MacJannet Foundation meeting at Priory, 1985; MS024.007.099.00005 (Box 99)
    - Talloires photographs, 1974; MS024.007.099.00006 (Box 99)
    - MacJannet's trip to USA photos, 1966; MS024.007.099.00007 (Box 99)
      First of two folders of snapshots.
    - MacJannet's trip to USA photos, 1966; MS024.007.099.00008 (Box 99)
      Second of two folders of snapshots.
    - Photos from Spain, Easter, 1933; MS024.007.099.00009 (Box 99)
      People; Buildings; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - Charlotte MacJannet in New Delhi, India 1959 with Nera and Indira Gandhi, MS024.007.099.00010 (Box 99)
      People; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Nehru, Jawaharlal; Gandhi, Indira
    - Loose photos from the "In honor of Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet" scrapbook, 1991; MS024.007.099.00011 (Box 99)
    - Loose photos from an Elms school scrapbook, 1930; MS024.007.099.00012 (Box 99)
      Photos were found at back of scrapbook
      Children; MacJannet School
    - Snapshots of friends, 1960; MS024.007.100.00001 (Box 100)
      From envelope labeled "Ilo and Gerda family"
    - Photos from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's family in Germany, 1915; MS024.007.100.00002 (Box 100)
      People; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet family photos, 1920; MS024.007.100.00003 (Box 100)
    - Snapshots of a Tufts reunion, 1950; MS024.007.100.00004 (Box 100)
      Alumni and alumnae
    - Photos from an envelope labled "Klossenleg", 1915; MS024.007.100.00005 (Box 100)
    - Photos from Salzburg, 1922; MS024.007.100.00006 (Box 100)
    - Photos of the Blensdorf family, 1910; MS024.007.100.00007 (Box 100)
    - Photos of Talloires, 1939; MS024.007.100.00008 (Box 100)
      MacJannet Camp
    - Personal snapshots sent to Charlotte and Donald MacJannet, 1975; MS024.007.100.00009 (Box 100)
    - Photos of camp 'Bourget', 1920; MS024.007.100.00010 (Box 100)
      Camp 'training' for D. MacJannet
      Children; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Photos from Arlington, vacation school of French, 1944; MS024.007.100.00011 (Box 100)
      MacJannets' school for French at their Arlington home
      Students; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Tufts College
    - Snapshots from trip to Italy, 1930; MS024.007.101.00001 (Box 101)
      People; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - Photos labeled as 'groups', 1930; MS024.007.101.00002 (Box 101)
      Includes some camp and school photos.
      Children
    - MacJannet snapshots, 1930; MS024.007.101.00003 (Box 101)
      From envelope labeled "Veyrier"
    - Photos from Mr. Mac's 90th birthday, Talloires, 1984; MS024.007.101.00004 (Box 101)
      MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Jean MacJannet Foster photos, 1945; MS024.007.101.00005 (Box 101)
      People; Buildings; Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - MacJannet photos of 'Anna Antik', 1920; MS024.007.101.00006 (Box 101)
    - MacJannet photos of St. Cloud school, 1930; MS024.007.101.00007 (Box 101)
      Children; The Elms; MacJannet School
    - Photos from Venezuela, 1935; MS024.007.101.00008 (Box 101)
      First of three folders. Includes written commentary (unknown author).
      Buildings
    - Photos from Venezuela, 1935; MS024.007.101.00009 (Box 101)
      Second of three folders. Includes written commentary (unknown author).
    - Photos from Venezuela, 1935; MS024.007.101.00010 (Box 101)
      Third of three folders. Includes written commentary (unknown author).
    - Photos from Arlington, vacation school of French, 1944; MS024.007.101.00012 (Box 100)
      Students; MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Tufts College
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet with Gerda Alexander in Italy, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03781; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-101#001 - "Italy"
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Alexander, Gerda
    - A young camper playing a musical instrument at the MacJannet Camp, 1950; MS024.007.DO.03782; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-101#002 - "Groups"
      People; Children; Music and musical performances; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Campers learning proper paddling techniques, 1950; MS024.007.DO.03783; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      People; Children; Canoes and canoeing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Raising the flags of the United States and France at the MacJannet Camp, 1950; MS024.007.DO.03784; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      People; Children; Flags; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
    - Campers relaxing on Lake Annecy, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03785; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-101#003 - "In envelope labeled 'Veyrier' (but personal and camp)"
    - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03786; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-101#007 - "Envelope labeled 'St. Cloud'"
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet receiving honorary degrees during the opening of the European Center at Talloires, 1979; MS024.007.DO.03787; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-099#001 - "Tufts honorary ceremony at the Priory/Talloires"
      People; Ceremonies; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; European Center
    - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet celebrating the opening of the European Center, 1979; MS024.007.DO.03788; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
    - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet ice skating, 1933; MS024.007.DO.03789; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-099#009 - "Spain - Easter, 1933"
      People; Ice Skating; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet with Prime Minister Jawaharlal Nehru in New Delhi, 1959; MS024.007.DO.03790; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-099#011 - "Charlotte in New Delhi with Nehru and Indira Gandhi, 1959"
      People; Government officials; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Nehru, Jawaharlal
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet with Indira Gandhi in New Delhi, 1959; MS024.007.DO.03791; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      People; Government officials; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Gandhi, Indira Priyadarshini Nehru
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet during a birthday celebration in her honor, 1991; MS024.007.DO.03792; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-099#011 - "Photos from 'In Honor of Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1991'"
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet receiving the title of "Citoyen d'Honneur de Talloires" during her birthday celebration, 1991; MS024.007.DO.03793; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
      taken from MS024/007-099#011 - "Photos from 'In honor of Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1991'"
      People; Awards; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet cutting her birthday cake, 1991; MS024.007.DO.03794; Unknown (Box Shared 120)
    - Young students finger painting at the Elms School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03795; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_856aa3493e396de6280376d6f5465c51)
      taken from MS024/007-099#012 - "Loose photos from MacJannet Elms School scrapbook"
    - A MacJannet School staff member with her young charges during an outing in Paris, 1932; MS024.007.DO.03796; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_856aa3493e396de6280376d6f5465c51)
    - MacJannet students and staff members photographed in front of the Eiffel Tower in Paris, 1932; MS024.007.DO.03797; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_856aa3493e396de6280376d6f5465c51)
      People; Staff; Students; Monuments; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet photos of family, friends, camp, and Sun Valley school, 1910 -- 1991; MS024.007.102
    - Photos of Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's family, 1930; MS024.007.102.00001 (Box 102)
      From envelope labeled 'enkelkinder'
    - Blensdorf photos from Sweden, 1925; MS024.007.102.00002 (Box 102)
    - Charlotte MacJannet's photos from Solsidan, Sweden, 1925; MS024.007.102.00003 (Box 102)
    - Photos from the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.102.00004 (Box 102)
    - Photos from mini album, 1980; MS024.007.102.00005 (Box 102)
    - Photos of 'Donald and Charlotte', 1915 -- 1986; MS024.007.102.00006 (Box 102)
      People; MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Blensdorf family photos, 1920; MS024.007.102.00007 (Box 102)
    - Blensdorf family, Germany, 1915; MS024.007.102.00008 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00009 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00010 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00011 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00012 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00013 (Box 102)
    - Photos of MacJannet Sun Valley school, 1941; MS024.007.102.00014 (Box 102)
    - Charlotte MacJannet photos, 1935; MS024.007.103.00001 (Box 103)
    - Photos of Charlotte MacJannet's family, 1925; MS024.007.103.00002 (Box 103)
    - Photographs of Charlotte MacJannet, 1960; MS024.007.103.00003 (Box 103)
    - Photographs from Nice, 1933; MS024.007.103.00004 (Box 103)
      Possibly trip when Donald MacJannet met Charlotte Blensdorf.
    - Blensdorf children and family photos, 1920; MS024.007.103.00005 (Box 103)
    - Photos of a wedding, 1960; MS024.007.103.00006 (Box 103)
      From envelope labled "Lotte."
    - Photos of Donald MacJannet, 1935; MS024.007.103.00007 (Box 103)
      People; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - MacJannet photos, 1980; MS024.007.103.00008 (Box 103)
    - Photos of Charlotte MacJannet's family, 1910 -- 1991; MS024.007.103.00009 (Box 103)
      Photos of Inge, Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's sister.
    - Photos of MacJannet clan and friends, 1960 -- 1980; MS024.007.103.00010 (Box 103)
    - Snapshots of friends, 1970; MS024.007.103.00011 (Box 103)
      From envelope labeled "Ilo"
    - Photos of helpers at the Priory, 1970; MS024.007.103.00012 (Box 103)
    - Personal photos, 1975; MS024.007.103.00013 (Box 103)
      From envelope labeled "Ole Groenliev"
    - Personal photos, 1966; MS024.007.103.00014 (Box 103)
    - MacJannet school photos, 1935; MS024.007.104.00001 (Box 104)
      Includes school trip and holiday photos.
    - MacJannet school photos, 1935; MS024.007.104.00002 (Box 104)
      Includes school trips and holiday photos.
    - MacJannet school photos, 1935; MS024.007.104.00003 (Box 104)
    - MacJannet school photos, 1935; MS024.007.104.00004 (Box 104)